Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
We finally meet the legendary Mandalorian.
We are so glad you agreed to work for us.
You will be very rich.
Of course. Mando.
Yes our poor nephew has been taken.
He fell in with a bad crowd.
We are heartbroken.
Ah yes.
The only image we have is from long ago.
He's had a growth spurt since then.
You will find him on the moon of Shakari.
Are you here to kill me?
Did you get the Mandalorian?
Very good. Bring him to Nal Hutta.
Pay the hunter.
Bring me his helmet.
You have entertained us.
Here is your reward.
Even if you win.
you will die from the poison.
Send the droids! Release the Amani!
Don't let him escape!
Repel the intruders!
Protect the palace!
Wait! We know much.
Stop!
You don't have Jabba to protect you.
I'm not little anymore!
Stop! You'll kill us all!
Save us. bounty hunter!
Save us!
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm